What! The screws are coming back?
What!
This is the second time.
What! I feel like I'm in good hands.
I'm so happy!
Okay!
Hello everyone, I'm Kaho Kobayashi, attendance number 11 from CTV Shugaku!
Last time we made a table.
What are you going to make this time?
I'm going to make a bench!
A bench!
Suddenly it sounds so difficult...
Wouldn't it be stylish to have a bench in the garden?
I'd love to have one...
Let's make it today!
Yes, sir! I'll do my best!
I do a lot of DIY on this channel, so please subscribe and rate my channel!
Please subscribe and rate my channel!
Let's make a bench!
Dogodogo DIY!
Mr. Kobayashi, a carpenter, will help me this time, too!
Thank you very much!
Let's get started!
Let's cut the legs of the bench!
Legs! Yes!
Cut 6 thick timbers!
And 400 more to go!
So, just like when we made the table
I'll have it measured.
Oh! I cut so much!
I felt like I was in charge.
I'm so happy!
Aren't you happy?
Oh, hey, hey, hey, hey.
But now...
The thing I held down the other day when I was working on the table here...
It's not wide enough.
I'm not using it this time.
I'll hold it.
I'm going to hold it, and I'm going to line it up with this.
Align them.
Yes, it's thicker again.
I can't cut it in one go.
So I'll cut it in two.
Yes, sir.
Yes, please.
I can't do it once, so I'll do it again.
Yes, sir.
I decided like this.
It's very difficult... but the other one's cutting... is already very good.
Really?
Yes.
That's good.
I just finished cutting the six legs.
What's next?
Well, I want to make it like this.
I'd like to drop this half down a little.
Oh, I see. It's a difficult one.
You want to take another half, and then take another half only.
Yes.
This is the one I made.
Like this.
Wow!
Yes.
Like this.
I see.
I'll have Mr. Kobashi make another one.
Yes, sir.
Another difficult one.
No, no, no, this is the second time.
Eeeeee... no...
Ha-ha-ha.
Okay.
Here you go.
Oh, wow!
Oh! Oh!
That feels good!
You can do it like this.
That's great.
I'd like to get this one. Can I do a little work here?
Yes, please.
I'll chew it nice and clean.
What is that? I don't know.
It's not safe for an amateur.
Yes, sir.
A table-top circular saw and a regular circular saw.
It's jagged like this now, right?
And again, just like before.
Wow!
And now, this part is left.
I'll have Mr. Kobayashi remove it.
Yes, sir.
You can flip it over, right?
It's flattened.
It's flattened out from here.
You're getting really good at this, aren't you?
What are you doing?What are you doing?
How are you doing, Mr. Okai?
Are you getting better?
No, I'm totally fine now.
I'm glad. I'm glad.
I used this for the part where you sit on your buttocks.
Use this for the back.
I'm going to cut a lot of this.
Yes, sir.
1700 mm.
1700 mm?
Yes. 1 meter 70 cm.
1 meter 70 centimeters.
Right here.
About my height?
About two or three people.
Yes.
Ending.
I'll make a lot of these.
Mmm-hmm.
Are you having fun?
It's fun.
Ha-ha-ha!
It's a lot of fun!
This time.
Yes.
This is the axis for the backrest.
Yes, sir.
Put it here like this.
Yes.
Attach the backrest here.
Yes, sir.
This is how it's processed.
At a slight angle.
It's difficult to do.
Yes.
If you do it, Mr. Kobayashi...
I'd like you to make something like this.
I would like you to go to a home improvement center or something like that.
and ask for advice.
There are places that make this kind of thing, right?
I see.
If you go to a home improvement center now, they will cut it for you, right?
That's right.
You can ask for advice at the place where you bought these things.
Yes.
You can ask them for advice like I did.
Oh, it's okay.
Please consult Mr. Kobayashi.
This way please.
Ha-ha-ha.
This is the second construction.
Amazing.
The one I've seen before.
Wow!
It fits.
It's just like this.
Someone uses this at home, right?
Yes, I do.
Someone who likes to do this kind of thing.
There are some for less than 10,000 yen at home improvement stores.
I thought they'd be more expensive.
There are affordable ones, too.
Yes, there are.
This kind of thing.
Wow!
Now it's time to assemble it.
Yes! Assembled!
It's kind of unstable, isn't it?
That's why we have to do it on the ground.
We're going to do it on the ground, right?
Yes, sir.
I guess we'll take a break.
Thank you very much.
A break.
Yes, thank you.
Log log DIY
Now that the materials have been cut, we can start assembling.
Now it's time to build the bench.
The legs are cut at 400.
Let's intertwine them.
Yes, yes, yes...
It's so fast, so fast!
It's getting faster! I'm so happy!
I'm so happy!
I'm so glad you're getting faster!
I did it!
Wow, great!
Wow, it looks like a bench.
And put it on like this
Oh, it's a bench already
That's great.
I'll stroke one first.
I'll take care of it.
Thank you very much.
That's nice. Like an assistant.
Like an assistant. I'm always ready to help out in the field.
These four are where your buttocks sit, right?
Yes, sir.
We want to open up the space between each one.I want to open the gap between each strand.
I see.
It's true that benches have gaps, don't they?
Yes, they are.
You could stick them together, but...
It's more stylish this way.
I don't know.
I just used this to make a gap.
The width of the gap is different.
Oh, that's right.
So I'll fix this a little.
Yes, it's difficult.
Can you fix it?
I'll fix it.
That gap.
Aaaaahhh!
Woooooooooooo!
Eeeeeeee...
Now we'll attach the backrest here.
Yes, sir.
That's hard to do.
What's straight
Yes!
Whoo!
Good!
You're getting better.
Ha-ha-ha!
I just laughed because I was talking so much.
I was in the middle of setting it down and it was already done.
The bench is finished!
Yay yay yay yay yay yay!
I think I'm going to grill some steaks.
Excuse me.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. I'm fine on my own.
Please stand up.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
It's all right.
It's sturdy.
Amazing!
So, the bench is completed.
So, I think it will be lonely if this is all I do.
I'm going to write a little bit about it, too, so I'll do it.
I will write!
Uh-huh!
Yes, like this.
I think it's good.
I like it, Po stands out!
Po stands out.
But by making the color a little yellow
But by making the color a little yellow, you can't really see the "po" at a glance.
Only those who do will recognize it.
I made it into a vedge.
Hmmm...
Log Log DIY
How did you like it? Today, I think it's a bench.
I didn't know what I could do, because I was really new to this.
I never thought I would be able to make a bench!
So I'm really excited now, and I think I'm going to be able to sleep super well!
Ha-ha-ha!
This is how I tried to make this bench.
If you think it's a good bench, please subscribe to the channel and give it a high rating!
I'm sure we'll be doing many more DIY projects on this channel.
I'm sure I'm having a lot of fun making DIY items on this channel.
Please watch this channel too!
That's all for now, this is Kaho Kobayashi as Shirutsu Ebissi!
Bye bye!
The product we used this time is this AS-05 safety shoes.
The shoe shape has been reviewed for a better fit and hold.
It is easy to walk with less foot shake even when walking!
Ideal for tentacles used in logistics, construction, and other areas where there are many opportunities to walk
Cool graphical design on the upper
Excellent grip, even on water or oil-covered floor surfaces.
If you are interested in this product, check out the overview section.
Please subscribe to our channel.